<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>[REP] Repentance Plus - New Items, Trinkets and Pockets!</name>
    <directory>repentanceplus</directory>
    <id>2627014611</id>
    <description>[h1]Welcome![/h1]
Repentance+ is a mod that adds (for now):
[list]
    [*] [strike]23[/strike] 26 new items;
    [*] 13 new trinkets;
    [*] [strike]22[/strike] 25 new cards;
    [*] [strike]2[/strike] 5 new pills;
    [*] 1 new chest
[/list] 
into the game!

This mod was designed to provide a more thorough Repentance experience, because it does what devs didn't want to do: brings [b]all remaining unlocks[/b], thematically fitting for tainted characters, into the game (awarding players new content for beating Greed mode, Boss Rush, Satan, Isaac and Blue Baby)!
[i]Please note[/i] that all new content is currently available from the get-go and isn't locked behind any achievements; making an achievement system will be our last step, we want to implement the content first.
[b]This mod doesn't unlock any vanilla achievement, and it won't even when the unlock system is introduced! [/b]

[h2]Our little team[/h2]
[list]
    [*] Mr. SeemsGood - lead programmer
    [*] erawalks - sprite artist and the man behind this whole idea for the mod (this mod exists only thanks to[url=https://www.reddit.com/r/bindingofisaac/comments/ommys1/had_the_idea_for_the_mod_but_then_i_realized_that/] this[/url] reddit post of his)
    [*] Kartoschka - programmer
    [*] people from our Discord server - small help with the code and organizing our work
[/list] 

[h2]Special thanks[/h2]
[list]
    [*] to Agent Cucco for her Red Map trinket mod, from where I learned some useful stuff for the Red Map item
    [*] to Woufsauge for providing a guide on how to apply persistent player costumes and Isaac Lua API docs
    [*] to KingBobson for his mod Run Continues Past Mother (the item we used this concept for was scrapped, so use his mod instead!)
    [*] to Onyx and his Achievement System mod for helping us understand how to implement the unlocks system!
    [*] to everyone from #modding-dev channel of Isaac Discord who helped create this mod!
    [*] to reddit user u/pijon95 for[url=https://www.reddit.com/r/bindingofisaac/comments/oodrci/all_missing_tainted_character_unlocks/] this post[/url] with ideas for all unlocks (we used these great ideas for couple of items, namely Temper Tantrum, Cherry Friends and Enraged Soul)
[/list]

[h2]I found a bug![/h2]
Please refer to Bug Report discussion section and submit the bug here. This mod is currently in beta-state, and in parallel to making new content, we will try to polish the existing pieces of the mod!
Also feel free to write suggestions for the new content. Creative and original entries will make it into the mod!

[h2]And don't forget to use EID (or Encyclopedia), yo![/h2]
Going in blind is never cool, so download this great mod by Wofsauge to see the descriptions for our items, trinkets and pocket items HERE: 

https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=836319872

Since version 1.7, our mod now supports (not fully) Spanish EID! Thanks to Discord user Kotry for that!
Also, the mod now supports the Encyclopedia mod by Agent Cucco, so get it HERE:

https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2376005362</description>
    <version>1.14</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
    <tag id="Items"/>
    <tag id="Active Items"/>
    <tag id="Trinkets"/>
    <tag id="Pills"/>
    <tag id="Cards"/>
    <tag id="Pickups"/>
    <tag id="Familiars"/>
</metadata>
